Guide to the Group Research, Inc. Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series IV: Group Research Report
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 9, no. 14, pages 53-6, July 31, 1970 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 9, no. 15, pages 57-60, September 10, 1970 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 9, no. 16, pages 61-4, October 21, 1970 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 9, no. 17, pages 65-8, November 25, 1970 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 9, no. 18, pages 69-72, December 15, 1970 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Index to vol. 9, nos. 1-18, 1970 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 10, no. 1, pages 1-4, January 8, 1971 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 10, no. 2, pages 5-8, February 9, 1971 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 10, no. 3, pages 9-12, March 3, 1971 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 10, no. 4, pages 13-6, March 22, 1971 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 10, no. 5, pages 17-20, April 5, 1971 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 10, no. 6, pages 21-4, April 23, 1971 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 10, no. 7, pages 25-8, May 14, 1971 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 10, no. 8, pages 29-32, June 3, 1971 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 10, no. 9, pages 33-6, June 30, 1971 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 10, no. 10, pages 37-40, August 20, 1971 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 10, no. 11, pages 41-4, September 14, 1971 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 10, no. 12, pages 45-8, October 14, 1971 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 10, no. 13, pages 49-52, October 30, 1971 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 10, no. 14, pages 53-6, November 17, 1971 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 10, no. 15, pages 57-60, December 21, 1971 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Index to vol. 10, nos. 1-15, 1971 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 11, no. 1, pages 1-4, January 10, 1972 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 11, no. 2, pages 5-8, January 27, 1972 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 11, no. 3, pages 9-12, February 15, 1972 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 11, no. 4, pages 13-6, February 29, 1972 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 11, no. 5, pages 17-20, March 20, 1972 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 11, no. 6, pages 21-4, April 5, 1972 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 11, no. 7, pages 25-8, April 26, 1972 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 11, no. 8, pages 29-32, May 15, 1972 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 11, no. 9, pages 33-6, May 31, 1972 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 11, no. 10, pages 37-40, June 30, 1972 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 11, no. 11, pages 41-4, July 26, 1972 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 11, no. 12, pages 45-8, August 23, 1972 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 11, no. 13, pages 49-52, September 18, 1972 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 11, no. 14, pages 53-6, October 2, 1972 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 11, no. 15, pages 57-60, October 26, 1972 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 11, no. 16, pages 61-4, November 20, 1972 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 11, no. 17, pages 65-8, December 13, 1972 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Index to vol. 11, nos. 1-17, 1972 (Box 428)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 12, no. 1, pages 1-4, February 15, 1973 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 12, no. 2, pages 5-8, March 9, 1973 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 12, no. 3, pages 9-12, March 20, 1973 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 12, no. 4, pages 13-6, April 9, 1973 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 12, no. 5, pages 17-20, April 25, 1973 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 12, no. 6, pages 21-4, May 18, 1973 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 12, no. 7, pages 25-8, June 5, 1973 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 12, no. 8, pages 29-32, June 13, 1973 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 12, no. 9, pages 33-6, September 13, 1973 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 12, no. 10, pages 37-40, September 28, 1973 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 12, no. 11, pages 41-4, October 16, 1973 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 12, no. 12, pages 45-8, October 31, 1973 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 12, no. 13, pages 49-52, November 28, 1973 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 12, no. 14, pages 53-6, December 17, 1973 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Index of vol. 12, nos. 1-14, 1973 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 13, no. 1, pages 1-4, January 28, 1974 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 13, no. 2, pages 5-8, February 25, 1974 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 13, no. 3, pages 9-12, March 26, 1974 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 13, no. 4, pages 13-6, April 30, 1974 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 13, no. 5, pages 17-20, May 24, 1974 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 13, no. 6, pages 21-4, June 24, 1974 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 13, no. 7, pages 25-8, August 3, 1974 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 13, no. 8, pages 29-32, September 3, 1974 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 13, no. 9, pages 33-6, October 4, 1974 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 13, no. 10, pages 37-40, October 30, 1974 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 13, no. 11, pages 41-4, December 19, 1974 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Index to vol. 13, nos. 1-11, 1974 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 14, no. 1, pages 1-4, January 28, 1975 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 14, no. 2, pages 5-8, February 26, 1975 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 14, no. 3, pages 9-12, March 26, 1975 (Box 429)
    [Folder empty -- issue missing.]
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 14, no. 4, pages 13-6, April 28, 1975 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 14, no. 5, pages 17-20, May 28, 1975 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 14, no. 6, pages 21-4, June 30, 1975 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 14, no. 7, pages 25-8, July 31, 1975 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 14, no. 8, pages 29-32, August 26, 1975 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 14, no. 9, pages 33-6, September 29, 1975 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 14, no. 10, pages 37-40, October 29, 1975 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 14, no. 11, pages 41-4, December 3, 1975 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 14, no. 12, pages 45-8, December 17, 1975 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Index of vol. 14, nos. 1-12, 1975 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 15, no. 1, pages 1-4, January 21, 1976 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 15, no. 2, pages 5-8, March 3, 1976 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 15, no. 3, pages 9-12, March 30, 1976 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 15, no. 4, pages 13-6, May 3, 1976 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 15, no. 5, pages 17-20, June 9, 1976 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 15, no. 6, pages 21-4, June 30, 1976 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 15, no. 7, pages 25-8, August 6, 1976 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 15, no. 8, pages 29-32, September 20, 1976 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 15, no. 9, pages 33-6, October 22, 1976 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 15, no. 10, pages 37-40, November 23, 1976 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 15, no. 11, pages 41-4, December 15, 1976 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Index of vol. 15, no. 1-11, 1976 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 16, no. 1, pages 1-4, January 20, 1977 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 16, no. 2, pages 5-8, February 28, 1977 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 16, no. 3, pages 9-12, March 30, 1977 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 16, no. 4, pages 13-6, April 20, 1977 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 16, no. 5, pages 17-20, May 31, 1977 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 16, no. 6, pages 21-4, June 29, 1977 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 16, no. 7, pages 25-8, July/August 1977 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 16, no. 8, pages 29-32, September 28, 1977 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 16, no. 9, pages 33-6, October 31, 1977 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 16, no. 10, pages 37-40, November 30, 1977 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 16, no. 11, pages 41-4, December 28, 1977 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Index of vol. 16, nos. 1-11, 1977 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 17, no. 1, pages 1-4, January 31, 1978 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 17, no. 2, pages 5-8, February 28, 1978 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 17, no. 3, pages 9-12, March 29, 1978 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 17, no. 4, pages 13-6, April 29, 1978 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 17, no. 5, pages 17-20, May 30, 1978 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 17, no. 6, pages 21-4, June 27, 1978 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 17, no. 7, pages 25-8, July/August 1978 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 17, no. 8, pages 29-32, September 27, 1978 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 17, no. 9, pages 33-6, October 31, 1978 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 17, no. 10, pages 37-40, November 27, 1978 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 17, no. 11, pages 41-4, December 28, 1978 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Index of vol. 17, nos. 1-11, 1978 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 18, no. 1, pages 1-4, January 29, 1979 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 18, no. 2, pages 5-8, February 28, 1979 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 18, no. 3, pages 9-12, March 23, 1979 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 18, no. 4, pages 13-6, April 20, 1979 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 18, no. 5, pages 17-20, May 22, 1979 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 18, no. 6, pages 21-4, June 27, 1979 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 18, no. 7, pages 25-8, July/August 1979 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 18, no. 8, pages 29-32, September 25, 1979 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 18, no. 9, pages 33-6, October 26, 1979 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 18, no. 10, pages 37-40, November 28, 1979 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 18, no. 11, pages 41-4, December 28, 1979 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Index of vol. 18, nos. 1-11, 1979 (Box 429)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 19, no. 1, pages 1-4, January 21, 1980 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 19, no. 2, pages 5-8, February 25, 1980 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 19, no. 3, pages 9-12, March 26, 1980 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 19, no. 4, pages 13-6, April 30, 1980 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 19, no. 5, pages 17-20, May 29, 1980 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 19, no. 6, pages 21-4, June 25, 1980 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 19, no. 7, pages 25-8, July/August 1980 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 19, no. 8, pages 29-32, September 29, 1980 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 19, no. 9, pages 33-6, October 22, 1980 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 19, no. 10, pages 37-40, November 26, 1980 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 19, no. 11, pages 41-4, December 22, 1980 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Index to vol. 19, nos. 1-11, 1980 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 20, no. 1, pages 1-4, January 23, 1981 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 20, no. 2, pages 5-8, February 27, 1981 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 20, no. 3, pages 9-12, March 25, 1981 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 20, no. 4, pages 13-6, April 30, 1981 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 20, no. 5, pages 17-20, May 19, 1981 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 20, no. 6, pages 21-4, June 26, 1981 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 20, no. 7, pages 25-8, July/August 1981 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 20, no. 8, pages 29-32, September 28, 1981 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 20, no. 9, pages 33-6, October 30, 1981 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 20, no. 10, pages 37-40, November 27, 1981 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 20, no. 11, pages 41-4, December 23, 1981 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Index to vol. 20, nos. 1-11, 1981 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 21, no. 1, pages 1-4, January 30, 1982 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 21, no. 2, pages 5-8, February 26, 1982 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 21, no. 3, pages 9-12, March 29, 1982 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 21, no. 4, pages 13-6, April 30, 1982 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 21, no. 5, pages 17-20, May 28, 1982 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 21, no. 6, pages 21-4, June 30, 1982 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 21, no. 7, pages 25-8, July/August 1982 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 21, no. 8, pages 29-32, September 30, 1982 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 21, no. 9, pages 33-6, October 1982 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 21, no. 10, pages 37-40, November 1982 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 21, no. 11, pages 41-4, December 1982 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Index to vol. 21, nos. 1-11, 1982 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 22, no. 1, pages 1-4, January 1983 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 22, no. 2, pages 5-8, February 1983 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 22, no. 3, pages 9-12, March 1983 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 22, no. 4, pages 13-6, April 1983 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 22, no. 5, pages 17-20, May 1983 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 22, no. 6, pages 21-4, June 1983 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 22, no. 7, pages 25-8, July/August 1983 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 22, no. 8, pages 29-32, September 1983 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 22, no. 9, pages 33-6, October 1983 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 22, no. 10, pages 37-40, November 1983 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 22, no. 11, pages 41-4, December 1983 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Index to vol. 22, nos. 1-11, 1983 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 23, no. 1, pages 1-4, January 1984 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 23, no. 2, pages 5-8, February 1984 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 23, no. 3, pages 9-12, March 1984 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 23, no. 4, pages 13-6, April 1984 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 23, no. 5, pages 17-20, May 1984 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 23, no. 6, pages 21-4, June 1984 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 23, no. 7, pages 25-8, July/August 1984 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 23, no. 8, pages 29-32, September 1984 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 23, no. 9, pages 33-6, October 1984 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 23, no. 10, pages 37-40, November 1984 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 23, no. 11, pages 41-4, December 1984 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Index to vol. 23, nos. 1-11, 1984 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 24, no. 1, pages 1-4, January 1985 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 24, no. 2, pages 5-8, February 1985 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 24, no. 3, pages 9-12, March 1985 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 24, no. 4, pages 13-6, April 1985 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 24, no. 5, pages 17-20, May 1985 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 24, no. 6, pages 21-4, June 1985 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 24, no. 7, pages 25-8, July/August 1985 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 24, no. 8, pages 29-32, September 1985 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 24, no. 9, pages 33-6, October 1985 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 24, no. 10, pages 37-40, November 1985 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 24, no. 11, pages 41-4, December 1985 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Index to vol. 24, nos. 1-11, 1985 (Box 430)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 25, no. 1, pages 1-4, January 1986 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 25, no. 2, pages 5-8, February 1986 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 25, no. 3, pages 9-12, March 1986 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 25, no. 4, pages 13-6, April 1986 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 25, no. 5, pages 17-20, May 1986 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 25, no. 6, pages 21-4, June 1986 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 25, no. 7, pages 25-8, July/August 1986 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 25, no. 8, pages 29-32, September/October 1986 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 25, no. 9, pages 33-6, November 1986 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 25, no. 10, pages 37-40, December 1986 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Index to vol. 25, nos. 1-10, 1986 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 26, no. 1, pages 1-4, January 1987 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 26, no. 2, pages 5-8, February 1987 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 26, no. 3, pages 9-12, March 1987 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 26, no. 4, pages 13-8, April/May 1987 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 26, no. 5, pages 19-22, June 1987 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 26, no. 6, pages 23-6, July/August 1987 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 26, no. 7, pages 27-30, September 1987 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 26, no. 8, pages 31-4, October 1987 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 26, no. 9, pages 35-8, November 1987 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 26, no. 10, pages 39-42, December 1987 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Index to vol. 26, nos. 1-10, 1987 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 27, no. 1, pages 1-6, January/February 1988 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 27, no. 2, pages 7-12, March/April 1988 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 27, no. 3, pages 13-8, Summer 1988 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 27, no. 4, pages 19-24, Winter 1988 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Index to vol. 27, nos. 1-4, 1988 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 28, no. 1, pages 1-6, Spring 1989 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 28, no. 2, pages 7-12, Summer 1989 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 28, no. 3, pages 13-8, Fall 1989 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 28, no. 4, pages 19-24, Winter 1989 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Index to vol. 28, nos. 1-4, 1989 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 29, no. 1, pages 1-6, January/February 1990 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 29, no. 2, pages 7-12, March/April 1990 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 29, no. 3, pages 13-8, May/June 1990 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 29, no. 4, pages 19-24, Summer 1990 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 29, no. 5, pages 25-30, November/December 1990 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Index to vol. 29, nos. 1-5, 1990 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 30, no. 1, pages 1-8, Spring 1991 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 30, no. 2, pages 9-14, May/June 1991 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 30, no. 3, pages 15-22, Fall 1991 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Index to vol. 30, nos. 1-3, 1991 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 31, no. 1, pages 1-6, Spring 1992 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 31, no. 2, pages 7-12, Summer 1992 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 31, no. 3, pages 13-6, Fall 1992 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 31, no. 4, pages 17-20, Winter 1992 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Index to vol. 31, nos. 1-4, 1992 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 32, no. 1, pages 1-6, February 1993 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 32, no. 2, pages 7-12, April 1993 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 32, no. 3, pages 13-8, June 1993 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 32, no. 4, pages 19-24, August 1993 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 32, no. 5, pages 25-30, November 1993 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Index to vol. 32, nos. 1-5, 1993 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 33, no. 1, pages 1-6, February 1994 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 33, no. 2, pages 7-14, April 1994 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 33, no. 3, pages 15-8, June 1994 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 33, no. 4, pages 19-24, November 1994 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Index to vol. 33, nos. 1-4, 1994 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 34, no. 1, pages 1-8, Spring 1995 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 34, no. 2, pages 9-14, Summer 1995 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Index to vol. 34, nos. 1-2, 1995 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Vol. 35, no. 1, pages 1-8, Spring 1996 (Box 431)
  - "Group Research Report" Index to vol. 35, no. 1, 1996 (Box 431)
- Series V: Printed Materials
  - Books, magazines, and booklets, 1960-85 (Box 432)
    [Includes materials on Richard Nixon, Ronald Reagan, and National Security Seminars.]
- Series VI: Audio/Visual
  - Record (33.3 rpm), Chicago, IL, Not dated (Box 433)
    [See also Series 1 -- We, The People!]
- Series VII: Group Research Directory
  - Group Research Directory Instructions and Organization (A-D) (Box 434)
  - Group Research Directory Organization (F-P) (Box 434)
  - Group Research Directory Organization (S-Z) and Individuals (A-L) (Box 434)
  - Group Research Directory Individuals (M-Z) (Box 434)
  - Group Research Directory Publications (A-V) (Box 434)
  - Group Research Directory Index for Special Reports and Special Reports, Nos. 1-9 (Box 435)
  - Group Research Directory Special Reports, Nos. 10-20 (Box 435)
- Series VIII: Card Files
  This is a series of 48 boxes of cards in three sub-series--Personal Names, Organizations, and States--which index and cross-reference the Group research Archives. The cards contain additional information not found in the files. This series has been fully microfilmed. Researchers are requested to use the microfilm rather than the original cards.
  - Subseries VIII.1: Personal Names
    - A (Box 436)
    - B - Benn (Box 437)
    - Benno - Bo (Box 438)
    - Br - Bur (Box 439)
    - Bus - Ch (Box 440)
    - Ci - Co (Box 441)
    - Cr - Del (Box 442)
    - Dem - Eas (Box 443)
    - Eat - Fla (Box 444)
    - Fle - Ga (Box 445)
    - Ge - Gri (Box 446)
    - Gro - Haw (Box 447)
    - Hay - Hop (Box 448)
    - Hor - John (Box 449)
    - Johns - Kh (Box 450)
    - Ki - Lan (Box 451)
    - Lap - Lo (Box 452)
    - Lu - Mc (Box 453)
    - Ma - Mer (Box 454)
    - Mes - Mr (Box 455)
    - Mu - Ol (Box 456)
    - Om - Ph (Box 457)
    - Pi - Red (Box 458)
    - Ree - Ros (Box 459)
    - Rot - Scr (Box 460)
    - Scu - Smith, F. (Box 461)
    - Smith, G. - Sti (Box 462)
    - Sto - Thom (Box 463)
    - Thon - U (Box 464)
    - Wa - We (Box 465)
    - Wh - Won (Box 466)
    - Woo - Z (Box 467)
  - Subseries VIII.2: Organizations
    - A - American C. (Box 467)
    - American D. - Br (Box 468)
    - Bu - Colo (Box 469)
    - Colt - D (Box 470)
    - E - Ham (Box 471)
    - Han - Li (Box 472)
    - Lo - Net (Box 473)
    - Neu - Rh (Box 474)
    - Ri - U (Box 475)
    - V - Z (Box 476)
  - Subseries VIII.3: States
    - A- California R. (Box 476)
    - California S. - D (Box 477)
    - F - Missouri (Box 478)
    - Montana - South Dakota (Box 479)
    - Tenn. - Wyoming (Box 480)
- Series IX: Publications
  - A - F (Box 481)
  - G - Poin (Box 482)
  - Pois - Z (Box 483)
- Series X: Correspondence
  - Fan Mail (Box 484)